<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fredholm</title><link>https://holmdev.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Fredholm</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://holmdev.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fetching Xresources made simple</title><link>https://holmdev.github.io/articles/fetching-xresources-made-simple/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holmdev.github.io/articles/fetching-xresources-made-simple/</guid><description>As can be seen in previous posts, I use a standalone window manager. I really love being in control of every little small thing and building things myself. I have also really grown to like when systems work together and especially when they work together dynamically. One of these systems is Xresources, which have allowed me to sync my themes over multiple applications/WMs. However, not every application/WM has support for accessing and trying to hack together a solution for connecting them is suboptimal.</description></item><item><title>Interesting things</title><link>https://holmdev.github.io/links/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holmdev.github.io/links/</guid><description>Here you have a bunch of links that I find interesting at the moment.
Wikipedia pages I find interesting ANSI escape code Rotation matrix Other XKQR (Check out this guy if you like Emacs, Linux, Programming or Stenography) The Elian Script NerdFonts</description></item><item><title>Creating a volume display script</title><link>https://holmdev.github.io/articles/creating-a-volume-display-script/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holmdev.github.io/articles/creating-a-volume-display-script/</guid><description>This year I finally moved to Linux from using Windows for 4.5 years. However, there are a few things I missed from Windows, especially being able to see the volume level while adjusting it even when using an application fullscreen. The included Qtile widget wasn&amp;rsquo;t doing it for me so I decided to make my own volume display using dunstify.
Important This script is made for a setup using PulseAudio or Pipewire (with pipewire-pulse) as an audio server and that has pamixer installed.</description></item><item><title>Creating an RGB Keyboard Legend</title><link>https://holmdev.github.io/articles/creating-an-rgb-keyboard-legend/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holmdev.github.io/articles/creating-an-rgb-keyboard-legend/</guid><description>I recently found this post, where user u/Rasie1 had created a script for displaying their i3 keybinds when certain modifier keys were pressed. I thought it looked really dope and that it would fit nicely with the rest of my keyboard-centric setup, so I made my own.
I decided to use OpenRGB for controlling my Blackwidow V2&amp;rsquo;s RGB, since it fits my needs very well and has been my main RGB solution since the beginning of my Linux journey.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://holmdev.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holmdev.github.io/about/</guid><description>General This site is mainly just a place for me to dump short &amp;ldquo;articles&amp;rdquo; about things I discover/create while using computer and technology. The themes for the articles are therefore mostly about things such as Linux, Emacs, and WMs.
About me Well, who am I? The short answer is: a giant nerd. The slightly longer answer: a guy with way too much free time on his hands. I spend most of that time programming things, ricing my setup or tinkering with technology in general.</description></item></channel></rss>